{
    "id": "Sociedad_27",
    "claim": "Ana Requena claims in her new book ‘Vibrant Feminism' the revolution of enjoyment and pleasure. Ana Requena Aguilar (Madrid, 1984) dedicates her book Vibrant Feminism: If there is no pleasure it is not our revolution to her grandmothers, women who have not had that choice to enjoy their sexuality as they have other generations. The first chapter begins with the anecdote that his suitcase didn't come out of the airport tape and he thought the reason was the vibrator he had inside. His book seeks to escape that modesty of openly speaking of one's desire and enjoyment. This journalist is a member of the founding team of Eldiario. is and currently exercises as editor-in-chief of gender. What motivated him to write this book?I was motivated by what happened to me on a trip to Paris, the anecdote of the suitcase and the vibrator. The shame I felt gave me a lot to think about, made a switch activate and made it clear that I had to write about this, about feminism from a point of view of enjoyment and pleasure and of all the stigmas that today we carry as modern as we believe ourselves. In the end, part of a conflict that is personal but I think it connected with a conflict that we somehow have all women with more or less intensity, and that's because prejudices, gender roles and stereotypes still hurt us a lot. One of his ideas is that there is no revolution without pleasure. In recent years we have focused on the demands that had to do with macho violence, especially sexual violence, and that has been a historical turning point, this collective rupture of silence. But I think it's worth a reflection on how we have to complete that speech so we don't stay in a kind of terrifying narrative in which sex only appears associated with violence and in which we appear only as victims. We have to complete this with another discourse that claims us as subjects of desire and that we can talk about sex and what we do want to combat stereotypes that often prevent us from being at ease in our lives, in our bodies and in our relationships. It's not about disqualifying fear, what I'm saying is that it can't be the only answer. Name some examples of women being judged for openly speaking about their sexuality. She points them out because our society is mired in the idea that sex is something to embarrass women with, something with which they can attack, hurt, despise and question us. In patriarchy women lose or gain status depending on how we relate to men, whether we are going to let ourselves be made, whether we are going to be more sluts or submissive, a whole system that hierarchizes us. Those comments seek that message of discipline for the recipient and for all the others. Were you afraid to expose yourself?Many times you feel that you can be taken less seriously by using certain language. Something that doesn't happen in the same way to male writers and journalists who also chronicle that first person and those biographical dyes without that affecting their seriousness and image. We still have a cost, especially if the chosen subject has to do with sex, motherhood, relationships. Do you think men and women are educated differently when it comes to living their sexuality?In the end we are educated and socialized differently. For masculinity sex is central, it is built on the idea of an active male, permanently desiring and that also seems legitimized to obtain that sex through many strategies, from giving alcohol to women because thus it will be easier to take them to bed, insistence, intimidation.. and on the contrary the socialization of women is based on the opposite idea, in that our sexuality is something more discreet, contained, almost always at the service of another end that is usually romantic love or liking others but not seen so much from one's own pleasure. There are women who still don't know their bodies well. There are midwives who tell you that there are women who come to birth preparation classes without knowing where their clitoris is or without knowing the pelvic floor or what shape their vagina has. The vulva has always been built from that idea of something dark, dirty, smelly, in which it is better not to inquire much, and that prevents us from self-knowledge. We can not only give information to women thought from the medical or biological point, but also of human beings that we want to enjoy. Is there still fear of being openly feminist?The term feminist women claim it with pride or at least many no longer reject it even if it may cost them to call it themselves. Evidently there are reluctances, the disqualification of feminism has always been a classic, when they associate it with hatred of men, that what you really want is to de-protect women or treat us as if they were victims, there are a series of maxims that continue to be repeated today. What role do men play in feminist discourse?Men play a very important role, we need them to open their own gap with regard to masculinities, with regard to how they are going to stand before this revolution that directly challenges them. They have their own work to do as individuals and collectively to think about what they are going to do to accelerate the change of men, because the change of women has accelerated greatly and the ones left behind are them. Do different ideologies exist in feminism?It cannot be denied that the history of feminism is diverse and plural. Liberal feminism has already existed in other times, another thing is that we do not lose sight of the fact that the feminist spirit is transformative and necessarily opposed to the conservative. I'm sorry.",
    "source": "elpais.com",
    "date": "11/01/2021",
    "veracity": 1,
    "claims": [
        {
            "claim": "Ana Requena claims in his women .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who claimed in his women on 11/01/2021?",
                    "answer": "Ana Requena"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Ana Requena claim in his women?",
                    "score": 0.7833,
                    "answers": "Ana|compound\tthat Ana Requena claims in his women|ccomp\this|poss\this women|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Ana Requena claims in his women?",
                    "score": 0.7144,
                    "answers": "on 11/01/2021|prep\tthat|mark"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does elpais.com say about Ana Requena?",
                    "score": 0.7039,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 11/01/2021 that Ana Requena claims in his women|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "women Ana Requena women book Vibrant Feminism: If there is no the anecdote that his suitcase didn't come out of the airport tape and he thought the reason was the vibrator he had inside it is not our revolution to the anecdote that his suitcase didn't come out of the airport tape and he thought the reason was the vibrator he had inside some examples of women being judged for openly speaking about their sexuality .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did elpais.com report on 11/01/2021",
                    "answer": "elpais.com reported on 11/01/2021 that women Ana Requena women book Vibrant Feminism: If there is no the anecdote that his suitcase didn't come out of the airport tape"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did the author of Vibrant Feminism say about the story?",
                    "score": 0.6792,
                    "answers": "women being judged for openly speaking about their sexuality|pcomp\topenly speaking about their sexuality|pcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many women were being judged for openly speaking about their sexuality?",
                    "score": 0.6235,
                    "answers": "inside some examples of women being judged for openly speaking about their sexuality|prep\tsome examples of women being judged for openly speaking about their sexuality|pobj\tof women being judged for openly speaking about their sexuality|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Vibrant Feminism?",
                    "score": 0.6228,
                    "answers": "Vibrant|compound\tabout their sexuality|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of the book Vibrant Feminism?",
                    "score": 0.6226,
                    "answers": "women Ana Requena women|nsubj\tAna Requena women|appos\tthat women Ana Requena women book Vibrant Feminism|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the origin of the story that a man's suitcase didn't come out of the airport tape?",
                    "score": 0.5959,
                    "answers": "the anecdote that his suitcase did n't come out of the airport tape|attr\tthe anecdote that his suitcase did n't come out of the airport tape|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "some examples of women being judged for openly speaking about their sexuality women who still don't know their bodies well some examples of women being judged for openly speaking about their sexuality their her new book ‘Vibrant Feminism' women who still don't know their bodies well their her new book ‘Vibrant Feminism' .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What are some examples of women being judged for openly speaking about their sexuality?",
                    "answer": "women who still don't know their bodies well"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Are women being judged for openly speaking about their sexuality?",
                    "score": 0.7671,
                    "answers": "women being judged for openly speaking about their sexuality women who still do n't know their bodies well|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who wrote the book \"Vibrant Feminism\"?",
                    "score": 0.7077,
                    "answers": "their her new book ‘ Vibrant Feminism ' women who still do n't know their bodies well their her new book ‘ Vibrant Feminism '|pobj\ttheir her new book ‘ Vibrant Feminism '|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Vibrant Feminism?",
                    "score": 0.6257,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 11/01/2021 that some examples of women being judged for openly speaking about their sexuality women who still do n't know their bodies well some examples of women being judged for openly speaking about their sexuality their her new book ‘ Vibrant Feminism ' women who still do n't know their bodies well their her new book ‘ Vibrant Feminism '|ROOT\tthat some examples of women being judged for openly speaking about their sexuality women who still do n't know their bodies well some examples of women being judged for openly speaking about their sexuality their her new book ‘ Vibrant Feminism ' women who still do n't know their bodies well their her new book ‘ Vibrant Feminism '|ccomp\twomen being judged for openly speaking about their sexuality their her new book ‘ Vibrant Feminism ' women who still do n't know their bodies well their her new book ‘ Vibrant Feminism '|pcomp\tfor openly speaking about their sexuality their her new book ‘ Vibrant Feminism ' women who still do n't know their bodies well their her new book ‘ Vibrant Feminism '|prep\tVibrant|compound\twomen who still do n't know their bodies well their her new book ‘ Vibrant Feminism '|appos\tVibrant|compound"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Vibrant Feminism about women who don't know their bodies well?",
                    "score": 0.6211,
                    "answers": "who still do n't know their bodies well|relcl\twho still do n't know their bodies well|relcl"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "his seeks to escape women modesty women that idea of something dark, dirty, smelly, in which it is better not to inquire much of one's desire and enjoyment.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported that he seeks to escape women modesty women that idea of something dark, dirty, smelly?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is elpais.com?",
                    "score": 0.4046,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 11/01/2021 that his seeks to escape women modesty women that idea of something dark , dirty , smelly , in which it is better not to inquire much of one 's desire and enjoyment|ROOT\ton 11/01/2021|prep\tthat|mark\this|nsubj\tthat his seeks to escape women modesty women that idea of something dark , dirty , smelly , in which it is better not to inquire much of one 's desire and enjoyment|ccomp\tto|aux\tto escape women modesty women that idea of something dark , dirty , smelly , in which it is better not to inquire much of one 's desire and enjoyment|xcomp\twomen|nmod\tmodesty|nmod\twomen modesty women|dobj\tthat|det\tthat idea of something dark , dirty , smelly , in which it is better not to inquire much of one 's desire and enjoyment|dobj\tof something dark , dirty , smelly , in which it is better not to inquire much of one 's desire and enjoyment|prep\tsomething dark , dirty , smelly , in which it is better not to inquire much of one 's desire and enjoyment|pobj\tdark|amod\t,|punct\tdirty|amod\t,|punct\tdark , dirty , smelly|amod\t,|punct\tin which|prep\twhich|pobj\tit|nsubj\tin which it is better not to inquire much of one 's desire and enjoyment|relcl\tbetter|acomp\tnot|neg\tto|aux\tnot to inquire much of one 's desire and enjoyment|xcomp\tmuch of one 's desire and enjoyment|dobj\tof one 's desire and enjoyment|prep\tone 's|poss\t's|case\tone 's desire and enjoyment|pobj\tand|cc\tenjoyment|conj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Ana Requena that idea of something dark, dirty, smelly, in which it is better not to inquire much a member of the founding team of Eldiario.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who was a member of the founding team of Eldiario?",
                    "answer": "Ana Requena"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What did Ana Requena say about the idea of dark, dirty, smelly, in which it is better to inquire much a member of the founding team of Eldiario?",
                    "score": 0.6087,
                    "answers": ",|punct\t,|punct\t,|punct\tto|aux"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Ana Requena's role in the Eldiario team?",
                    "score": 0.5835,
                    "answers": "a member of the founding team of Eldiario|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "is and currently exercises male writers and journalists who also chronicle that first person and those biographical dyes without that affecting their seriousness and image feminist?The term feminist in-chief feminist?The term feminist male writers and journalists who also chronicle that first person and those biographical dyes without that affecting their seriousness and image .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the term feminist in-chief feminist?",
                    "answer": "male writers and journalists who also chronicle that first person and those biographical dyes without that affecting their seriousness and image"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does the term \"Feminist in-chief feminist\" mean?",
                    "score": 0.6005,
                    "answers": "term feminist male writers and journalists who also chronicle that first person and those biographical dyes without that affecting their seriousness and image|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the meaning of the term feminist in-chief feminist?",
                    "score": 0.5481,
                    "answers": "male|amod\tjournalists|conj\tthat first person and those biographical dyes|dobj\tbiographical|amod\tthat affecting their seriousness and image|pcomp\ttheir|poss\ttheir seriousness and image|dobj\tmale|amod\tjournalists|conj\tthat first person and those biographical dyes|dobj\tbiographical|amod\tthat affecting their seriousness and image|pcomp\ttheir|poss\ttheir seriousness and image|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the definition of a feminist?",
                    "score": 0.5301,
                    "answers": "on 11/01/2021|prep\tfeminist?The|ROOT\tfeminist in - chief|appos\tfeminist?The|appos\tfeminist|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does elpais.com do?",
                    "score": 0.5128,
                    "answers": "currently|advmod\tcurrently exercises male writers and journalists who also chronicle that first person and those biographical dyes without that affecting their seriousness and image|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is elpais.com?",
                    "score": 0.4454,
                    "answers": "elpais.com|nsubj\telpais.com reported on 11/01/2021 that is and currently exercises male writers and journalists who also chronicle that first person and those biographical dyes without that affecting their seriousness and image|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "that motivated Ana Requena that write his was motivated by what happened to Ana Requena that speech a trip to Paris, our you many her new book ‘Vibrant Feminism' I .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did elpais.com report that Ana Requena was motivated to write?",
                    "answer": "11/01/2021"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What motivated Ana Requena to write her book \"Vibrant Feminism?",
                    "score": 0.8294,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 11/01/2021 that that motivated Ana Requena that write his was motivated by what happened to Ana Requena that speech a trip to Paris , our you many her new book ‘ Vibrant Feminism ' I|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Ana Requena write in her book \"Vibrant Feminism\"?",
                    "score": 0.7311,
                    "answers": "our you many her new book ‘ Vibrant Feminism '|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was Ana Requena's role in the writing of Vibrant Feminism I?",
                    "score": 0.6932,
                    "answers": "write|dep\this|nsubjpass\twhat|nsubj\ta|det\tto Paris|prep\t'|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Ana Requena's speech?",
                    "score": 0.633,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tthat|nsubj\tthat|nsubjpass\twas|auxpass\tthat|det\tthat speech|dep\tmany|dep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the name of Ana Requena's book?",
                    "score": 0.6028,
                    "answers": "Ana|compound\tAna|compound\tour|poss\tour you|nmod\ther|poss\tnew|amod\t‘|punct\tVibrant|compound\t‘ Vibrant Feminism '|appos\tI|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "I many I many I and made I clear many Ana Requena had to write about this, about feminism from a point of view of many and pleasure and of all the fear that today we carry as modern as we believe many .",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who wrote about feminism from a point of view of many and pleasure?",
                    "answer": "Ana Requena"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Ana Requena writing about feminism?",
                    "score": 0.6449,
                    "answers": "a point of view of many and pleasure and of all the fear that today we carry as modern as we believe many|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does elpais.com say about feminism?",
                    "score": 0.5838,
                    "answers": "to write about this , about feminism from a point of view of many and pleasure and of all the fear that today we carry as modern as we believe many|xcomp\tabout this , about feminism from a point of view of many and pleasure and of all the fear that today we carry as modern as we believe many|prep\tabout feminism from a point of view of many and pleasure and of all the fear that today we carry as modern as we believe many|prep\tfeminism from a point of view of many and pleasure and of all the fear that today we carry as modern as we believe many|pobj\tthat today we carry as modern as we believe many|relcl\tas modern as we believe many|advmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Requena say about the fear that we carry as modern as we believe many?",
                    "score": 0.5182,
                    "answers": "made I clear many Ana Requena had to write about this , about feminism from a point of view of many and pleasure and of all the fear that today we carry as modern as we believe many|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does elpais.com do?",
                    "score": 0.4055,
                    "answers": "this|pobj\tall|predet\twe|nsubj\twe|nsubj\tas we believe many|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is elpais.com?",
                    "score": 0.3373,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 11/01/2021 that I many I many I and made I clear many Ana Requena had to write about this , about feminism from a point of view of many and pleasure and of all the fear that today we carry as modern as we believe many|ROOT\tthat|mark\tI|nmod\tI|nmod\tand|cc\tI|nsubj\tto|aux\t,|punct\ta|det\tand|cc\tand|cc\tthe|det\tthat|dobj\tas|advmod\tas|mark"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "women the end, part of a conflict that is women but Ana Requena think it connected with a conflict women we somehow have all women with masculinity prejudices, gender roles and stereotypes still hurt us a lot.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who thought that women the end was connected with a conflict that is women?",
                    "answer": "Ana Requena"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does Ana Requena think about conflict women?",
                    "score": 0.5914,
                    "answers": "Ana|compound\tAna Requena think it connected with a conflict women we somehow have all women with masculinity prejudices , gender roles and stereotypes|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What did Ana Requena say about the conflict between men and women?",
                    "score": 0.5594,
                    "answers": "on 11/01/2021|prep\tthat|mark\tthe|det\t,|punct\tof a conflict that is women|prep\tthat|nsubj\tthat is women|relcl\tbut|cc\tit|nsubj\twe|nsubj\tsomehow|advmod\twomen we somehow have all women with masculinity prejudices , gender roles and stereotypes|acl\tall|det\tall women|dobj\t,|punct\tand|cc\tstill|advmod\tstill hurt us a lot|dep\tus|dobj\ta lot|npadvmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does it mean to be a conflict woman?",
                    "score": 0.5324,
                    "answers": "it connected with a conflict women we somehow have all women with masculinity prejudices , gender roles and stereotypes|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between a conflict woman and a conflict man?",
                    "score": 0.4864,
                    "answers": "a|det\ta|det\ta|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the definition of masculinity?",
                    "score": 0.4858,
                    "answers": "masculinity|compound"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "One of his ideas is that there is no revolution without pleasure.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did elpais.com report that one of his ideas was that there is no revolution without pleasure?",
                    "answer": "11/01/2021"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of his ideas on revolution without pleasure?",
                    "score": 0.6621,
                    "answers": "of his ideas|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is elpais.com?",
                    "score": 0.504,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 11/01/2021 that One of his ideas is that there is no revolution without pleasure|ROOT\ton 11/01/2021|prep\tthat|mark\tOne of his ideas|nsubj\this|poss\this ideas|pobj\tthat One of his ideas is that there is no revolution without pleasure|ccomp\tthat|mark\tthere|expl\tthat there is no revolution without pleasure|ccomp\tno|det\tno revolution without pleasure|attr\twithout pleasure|prep\tpleasure|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In recent years we have focused on the demands that had sex do with macho violence, especially sexual violence, and that has been a historical turning point, this collective rupture of silence.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 11/01/2021 that in recent years we have focused on the demands that had sex do with macho violence?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the demands for macho violence and sexual violence?",
                    "score": 0.5628,
                    "answers": "recent|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is macho violence?",
                    "score": 0.518,
                    "answers": "the demands that had sex do with macho violence , especially sexual violence|pobj\tdo with macho violence , especially sexual violence|acl\twith macho violence , especially sexual violence|prep\tmacho|amod\tmacho violence , especially sexual violence|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the definition of macho violence?",
                    "score": 0.515,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 11/01/2021 that In recent years we have focused on the demands that had sex do with macho violence , especially sexual violence , and that has been a historical turning point , this collective rupture of silence|ROOT\ton 11/01/2021|prep\tthat|mark\twe|nsubj\thave|aux\tthe|det\tthat|nsubj\tthat had sex|relcl\tsex|dobj\t,|punct\tespecially|advmod\tsexual|amod\tespecially sexual violence|appos\t,|punct\tand|cc\tthat|nsubj\thas|aux\ta|det\t,|punct\tthis|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What was the purpose of the collective rupture of silence?",
                    "score": 0.4927,
                    "answers": "that In recent years we have focused on the demands that had sex do with macho violence , especially sexual violence , and that has been a historical turning point , this collective rupture of silence|ccomp\tthat has been a historical turning point , this collective rupture of silence|conj\ta historical turning point , this collective rupture of silence|attr\tthis collective rupture of silence|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the meaning of silence?",
                    "score": 0.4633,
                    "answers": "silence|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "But I think it's worth a reflection on how we have to complete that speech so we don't stay in a kind of terrifying narrative in which sex only appears associated with violence and in which we appear only as victims.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 11/01/2021 that But I think it's worth a reflection on how we have to complete that speech?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does elpais.com say about sex and violence?",
                    "score": 0.499,
                    "answers": "how to complete that speech so we do n't stay in a kind of terrifying narrative in which sex only appears associated with violence and in which we appear only as victims|xcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between sex and violence?",
                    "score": 0.4878,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 11/01/2021 that But I think it 's worth a reflection on we have how to complete that speech so we do n't stay in a kind of terrifying narrative in which sex only appears associated with violence and in which we appear only as victims|ROOT\ton 11/01/2021|prep\tthat|mark\tBut|cc\tI|nsubj\tit|nsubj\tworth a reflection on we have how to complete that speech so we do n't stay in a kind of terrifying narrative in which sex only appears associated with violence and in which we appear only as victims|acomp\ta|det\thow|advmod\twe|nsubj\tto|aux\tthat|det\tthat speech|dobj\tso|mark\twe|nsubj\tdo|aux\tn't|neg\tso we do n't stay in a kind of terrifying narrative in which sex only appears associated with violence and in which we appear only as victims|advcl\tin a kind of terrifying narrative in which sex only appears associated with violence and in which we appear only as victims|prep\ta|det\ta kind of terrifying narrative in which sex only appears associated with violence and in which we appear only as victims|pobj\tof terrifying narrative in which sex only appears associated with violence and in which we appear only as victims|prep\tterrifying|amod\tterrifying narrative in which sex only appears associated with violence and in which we appear only as victims|pobj\tin which|prep\twhich|pobj\tsex|nsubj\tonly|advmod\tappears|aux\tin which sex only appears associated with violence and in which we appear only as victims|relcl\twith violence|prep\tviolence|pobj\tand|cc\tin which|prep\twhich|pobj\twe|nsubj\tin which we appear only as victims|conj\tonly|advmod\tonly as victims|prep\tvictims|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "We have to complete this with another discourse that claims us as subjects of desire and that we can talk about sex and what we do want to combat stereotypes that often prevent us from being at ease in our lives, in our bodies and in our relationships.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 11/01/2021 that we have to complete this with another discourse that claims us as subjects of desire?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does elpais.com say about sex and desire?",
                    "score": 0.5904,
                    "answers": "of desire|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between sex and sexuality?",
                    "score": 0.5412,
                    "answers": "our relationships|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the subject of desire?",
                    "score": 0.5224,
                    "answers": "subjects of desire|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does elpais.com do to combat stereotypes?",
                    "score": 0.5146,
                    "answers": "what we do want to combat stereotypes that often prevent us from being at ease in our lives , in our bodies and in our relationships|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the stereotypes that prevent us from being at ease in our lives, in our bodies and in our relationships?",
                    "score": 0.4918,
                    "answers": "stereotypes that often prevent us from being at ease in our lives , in our bodies and in our relationships|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "It's not about disqualifying fear, what I'm saying is that it can't be the only answer.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 11/01/2021 that it's not about disqualifying fear?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does elpais.com say about fear?",
                    "score": 0.7436,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 11/01/2021 that It 's not about disqualifying fear , what I 'm saying is that it ca n't be the only answer|ROOT\ton 11/01/2021|prep\tthat|mark\tIt|nsubj\tIt 's not about disqualifying fear|ccomp\tnot|neg\t,|punct\twhat|dobj\tI|nsubj\t'm|aux\twhat I 'm saying|csubj\tthat It 's not about disqualifying fear , what I 'm saying is that it ca n't be the only answer|ccomp\tthat|mark\tit|nsubj\tca|aux\tn't|neg\tthat it ca n't be the only answer|ccomp\tthe|det\tonly|amod\tthe only answer|attr"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the definition of disqualifying fear?",
                    "score": 0.7104,
                    "answers": "about disqualifying fear|prep\tdisqualifying fear|pcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is fear?",
                    "score": 0.7033,
                    "answers": "fear|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Name some examples of women being judged for openly speaking about their sexuality.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What did elpais.com report on 11/01/2021?",
                    "answer": "some examples of women being judged for openly speaking about their sexuality"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Are women being judged for openly speaking about their sexuality?",
                    "score": 0.8875,
                    "answers": "of women being judged for openly speaking about their sexuality|prep\twomen being judged for openly speaking about their sexuality|pcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is elpais.com?",
                    "score": 0.5406,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 11/01/2021 that Name some examples of women being judged for openly speaking about their sexuality|ROOT\ton 11/01/2021|prep\tbeing|auxpass"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "She points them out because our society is mired in the idea that sex is something to embarrass women with, something with which they can attack, hurt, despise and question us.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Why did elpais.com point out sex?",
                    "answer": "because our society is mired in the idea that sex is something to embarrass women with, something with which they can attack, hurt, despise and question us"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does elpais.com say about the idea that sex is something to embarrass women?",
                    "score": 0.6382,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tthem|dobj\tis|auxpass\tthe|det\tthat|mark\tto|aux\twith|prep\t,|punct\twhich|pobj\t,|punct\t,|punct\tand|cc"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does it mean to attack, hurt, and question us?",
                    "score": 0.5695,
                    "answers": "question us|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between sex and politics?",
                    "score": 0.5452,
                    "answers": "women|dobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "In patriarchy women lose or gain status depending on how we relate to men, whether we are going to let ourselves be made, whether we are going to be more sluts or submissive, a whole system that hierarchizes us.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported that in patriarchy women lose or gain status depending on how we relate to men?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many sluts or submissive are there in patriarchy?",
                    "score": 0.618,
                    "answers": "to be more sluts or submissive|xcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does elpais.com say about whether or not women lose or gain status?",
                    "score": 0.5816,
                    "answers": "depending on how we relate to men|prep\thow|advmod\thow we relate to men|pcomp\twhether|mark\tbe|auxpass\twhether|mark"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the system that hierarchizes us?",
                    "score": 0.5396,
                    "answers": "status whether we are going to let ourselves be made , whether we are going to be more sluts or submissive , a whole system that hierarchizes us|dobj\twhether we are going to let ourselves be made|advcl\twhether we are going to be more sluts or submissive|parataxis\ta|det\twhole|amod\twhether we are going to let ourselves be made , whether we are going to be more sluts or submissive , a whole system that hierarchizes us|appos\tthat hierarchizes us|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the relationship between men and women in the patriarchy?",
                    "score": 0.5301,
                    "answers": "In patriarchy|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between sluts and submissive?",
                    "score": 0.5299,
                    "answers": "that In patriarchy women lose or gain status whether we are going to let ourselves be made , whether we are going to be more sluts or submissive , a whole system that hierarchizes us depending on how we relate to men ,|ccomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Those comments seek that message of discipline for the recipient and for all the others.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 11/01/2021 that those comments seek that message of discipline for the recipient and all the others?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does elpais.com say about the message of discipline for recipients?",
                    "score": 0.637,
                    "answers": "that message of discipline|dobj\tall|predet"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does elpais.com seek for the recipient and for others?",
                    "score": 0.5724,
                    "answers": "for the recipient and for all the others|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of elpais.com?",
                    "score": 0.4625,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 11/01/2021 that Those comments seek that message of discipline for the recipient and for all the others|ROOT\ton 11/01/2021|prep\tthat|mark\tThose|det\tthat|det\tthe|det\tand|cc\tthe|det"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Were you afraid to expose yourself?Many times you feel that you can be taken less seriously by using certain language.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did elpais.com report that you were afraid to expose yourself?",
                    "answer": "11/01/2021"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does elpais.com say about using certain languages?",
                    "score": 0.6848,
                    "answers": "times you feel that you can be taken less seriously by using certain language|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the benefits of using certain language to expose yourself?",
                    "score": 0.6505,
                    "answers": "to expose|xcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the difference between using certain languages and not using certain language?",
                    "score": 0.5894,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tthat|mark\tbe|auxpass"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is elpais.com?",
                    "score": 0.4855,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 11/01/2021 that Were you afraid to expose yourself?Many times you feel that you can be taken less seriously by using certain language|ROOT\ton 11/01/2021|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Something that doesn't happen in the same way to male writers and journalists who also chronicle that first person and those biographical dyes without that affecting their seriousness and image.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 11/01/2021 that something that doesn't happen in the same way to male writers and journalists?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does elpais.com say about a male journalist who chronicle the first person and those biographical dyes?",
                    "score": 0.5648,
                    "answers": "male writers and journalists who also chronicle that first person and those biographical dyes without that affecting their seriousness and image|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does elpais.com do?",
                    "score": 0.5042,
                    "answers": "does|aux\tthose|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the meaning of the term \"first person\"?",
                    "score": 0.5017,
                    "answers": "their seriousness and image|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is elpais.com?",
                    "score": 0.4088,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 11/01/2021 that Something that does n't happen in the same way to male writers and journalists who also chronicle that first person and those biographical dyes without that affecting their seriousness and image|ROOT\tjournalists|conj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "We still have a cost, especially if the chosen subject has to do with sex, motherhood, relationships.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did elpais.com report that we still have a cost?",
                    "answer": "11/01/2021"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the cost of motherhood?",
                    "score": 0.6086,
                    "answers": "motherhood|appos"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does elpais.com say about the cost of sex, motherhood, and relationships?",
                    "score": 0.5694,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 11/01/2021 that We still have a cost , especially if the chosen subject has to do with sex , motherhood , relationships|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Do you think men and women are educated differently when it comes to living their sexuality?In the end we are educated and socialized differently.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 11/01/2021 that Do you think men and women are educated differently when it comes to living their sexuality?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the relationship between sexuality and education?",
                    "score": 0.6655,
                    "answers": "sexuality?In the end|punct"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does elpais.com say about living their sexuality?",
                    "score": 0.6326,
                    "answers": "on 11/01/2021|prep\tthat|mark\tyou|nsubj\twhen|advmod\tit|nsubj\twhen it comes to living their|advcl\tto living their|prep\tliving their|pcomp\tthe|det"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is elpais.com?",
                    "score": 0.4789,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 11/01/2021 that Do you think men and women are educated differently when it comes to living their sexuality?In the end we are educated and socialized differently|ROOT"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "For masculinity sex is central, it is built on the idea of an active male, permanently desiring and that also seems legitimized to obtain that sex through many strategies, from giving alcohol to women because thus it will be easier to take them to bed, insistence, intimidation.. and on the contrary the socialization of women is based on the opposite idea, in that our sexuality is something more discreet, contained, almost always at the service of another end that is usually romantic love or liking others but not seen so much from one's own pleasure.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the opposite of the idea that socialization of women is based on?",
                    "answer": "socialization of women is based on the opposite idea, in that our sexuality is something more discreet, contained, almost always at the service of another end that is usually romantic love or liking others but not seen so much from one's own pleasure"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What strategies are used to obtain that sex through many strategies?",
                    "score": 0.7993,
                    "answers": "that For masculinity sex is central , it is built on the idea of an active male , permanently desiring and that also seems legitimized to obtain that sex through many strategies , from giving alcohol to women because thus it will be easier to take them to bed , insistence , intimidation ..|ccomp\tinsistence|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does elpais.com say about men and women's sexuality?",
                    "score": 0.71,
                    "answers": "on the opposite idea , in that our sexuality is something more discreet , contained , almost always at the service of another end that is usually romantic love or liking others but not seen so much from one 's own pleasure|prep\tthe opposite idea , in that our sexuality is something more discreet , contained , almost always at the service of another end that is usually romantic love or liking others but not seen so much from one 's own pleasure|pobj\tin that our sexuality is something more discreet , contained , almost always at the service of another end that is usually romantic love or liking others but not seen so much from one 's own pleasure|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the idea of an active male being permanently desiring?",
                    "score": 0.6756,
                    "answers": "permanently desiring|amod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the definition of masculinity sex?",
                    "score": 0.6742,
                    "answers": "masculinity|pobj\tsex|nsubj\tit|nsubjpass\tseems|aux\tthat sex|dobj\tit|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the basis of masculinity sex?",
                    "score": 0.6728,
                    "answers": "For masculinity|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "There are women who still don't know their bodies well.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did elpais.com report that there are women who still don't know their bodies well?",
                    "answer": "11/01/2021"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many women don't know their bodies well?",
                    "score": 0.8201,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tThere|expl\twho|nsubj\tstill|advmod\tdo|aux\tn't|neg"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many women know their bodies well on elpais.com?",
                    "score": 0.657,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 11/01/2021 that There are women who still do n't know their bodies well|ROOT\ton 11/01/2021|prep"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "There are midwives who tell you that there are women who come to birth preparation classes without knowing where their clitoris is or without knowing the pelvic floor or what shape their vagina has.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What part of the pelvis do midwives not know about women who come to birth preparation classes?",
                    "answer": "pelvic floor"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "Are there midwives who come to birth preparation classes without knowing where their clitoris is?",
                    "score": 0.8312,
                    "answers": "on 11/01/2021|prep\tThere|expl\twho|nsubj\tyou|dobj\tthere|expl\twho|nsubj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many midwives work for childbirth preparation classes?",
                    "score": 0.6648,
                    "answers": "birth preparation|compound\twhat shape|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many midwives attend childbirth preparation classes?",
                    "score": 0.6547,
                    "answers": "birth preparation classes|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "The vulva has always been built from that idea of something dark, dirty, smelly, in which it is better not to inquire much, and that prevents us from self-knowledge.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did elpais.com report that The vulva was built from the idea of something dark, dirty, smelly?",
                    "answer": "11/01/2021"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What does it mean to inquire into the vulva?",
                    "score": 0.6685,
                    "answers": "in which it is better not to inquire much , and that prevents us from self - knowledge|relcl\tnot to inquire much|xcomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does elpais.com say about the vulva?",
                    "score": 0.6225,
                    "answers": "always|advmod"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of the vulva being built from?",
                    "score": 0.6177,
                    "answers": "that idea of something dark , dirty , smelly , in which it is better not to inquire much , and that prevents us from self - knowledge|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of the vulva?",
                    "score": 0.608,
                    "answers": "that The vulva has always been built from that idea of something dark , dirty , smelly , in which it is better not to inquire much , and that prevents us from self - knowledge|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the origin of the word vulva?",
                    "score": 0.6054,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 11/01/2021 that The vulva has always been built from that idea of something dark , dirty , smelly , in which it is better not to inquire much , and that prevents us from self - knowledge|ROOT\ton 11/01/2021|prep\tthat|mark\tThe|det\thas|aux\tbeen|auxpass\tthat|det\t,|punct\t,|punct\t,|punct\tin which|prep\twhich|pobj\tit|nsubj\tnot|neg\tto|aux\tmuch|dobj\t,|punct\tand|cc\tthat|nsubj\t-|punct"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "We can not only give information to women thought from the medical or biological point, but also of human beings that we want to enjoy.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "When did elpais.com report that we can not only give information to women thought from the medical or biological point?",
                    "answer": "11/01/2021"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What information does elpais.com give to women?",
                    "score": 0.7596,
                    "answers": "information|dobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does elpais.com say about women?",
                    "score": 0.5727,
                    "answers": "not only|preconj\tthat We can not only give information to women thought from the medical or biological point , but also of human beings we want that to enjoy|ccomp\tto women thought|dative\tmedical or biological|amod\tthe medical or biological point|pobj\tbut also|cc"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the purpose of elpais.com?",
                    "score": 0.3927,
                    "answers": "we want that to enjoy|relcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is elpais.com?",
                    "score": 0.3884,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 11/01/2021 that We can not only give information to women thought from the medical or biological point , but also of human beings we want that to enjoy|ROOT\ton 11/01/2021|prep\tthat|mark\tWe|nsubj\tonly|advmod\tthought|acl\tfrom the medical or biological point , but also of human beings we want that to enjoy|prep\tthe|det\tor|cc\tbiological|conj\t,|punct\talso|advmod\tthat|dobj\twe|nsubj\tto|aux\tthat to enjoy|xcomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Is there still fear of being openly feminist?The term feminist women claim it with pride or at least many no longer reject it even if it may cost them to call it themselves.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 11/01/2021 that Is there still fear of being openly feminist?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many women reject being openly feminist even if it cost them to call it themselves?",
                    "score": 0.8158,
                    "answers": "still|advmod\tpride|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does elpais.com say about being openly feminist?",
                    "score": 0.7714,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 11/01/2021 that Is there still fear of being openly feminist?The term feminist women claim it with pride or at least many no longer reject it even if it may cost them to call it themselves|ROOT\tor|cc\tno|neg"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the fear of being openly feminist?",
                    "score": 0.7701,
                    "answers": "that Is there still fear of being openly|ccomp\tfear of being openly|attr\tof being openly|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the definition of being a feminist?",
                    "score": 0.6988,
                    "answers": "being openly|pcomp"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Evidently there are reluctances, the disqualification of feminism has always been a classic, when they associate it with hatred of men, that what you really want is to de-protect women or treat us as if they were victims, there are a series of maxims that continue to be repeated today.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 11/01/2021 that Evidently there are reluctances?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What are the reasons for resigning from feminism?",
                    "score": 0.6348,
                    "answers": "Evidently there are reluctances|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the disqualification of feminism?",
                    "score": 0.6194,
                    "answers": "that Evidently there are reluctances , the disqualification of feminism has always been a classic , when they associate it with hatred of men , that what you really want is to de - protect women or treat us as if they were victims , there are a series of maxims that continue to be repeated today|ccomp"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the definition of disqualification of feminism?",
                    "score": 0.6069,
                    "answers": "on 11/01/2021|prep\tthat|mark\tEvidently|advmod\tthere|expl\t,|punct\tthe|det\tthe disqualification of feminism|nsubj\tof feminism|prep\tfeminism|pobj\thas|aux\talways|advmod\tthe disqualification of feminism has always been a classic|ccomp\ta|det\ta classic|attr\t,|punct\twhen|advmod\tthey|nsubj\twhen they associate it with hatred of men|advcl\tit|dobj\tof men|prep\tmen|pobj\t,|punct\tthat|mark\twhat|dobj\tyou|nsubj\treally|advmod\tto|aux\tto de|xcomp\t-|xcomp\tprotect women or treat us as if they were victims|xcomp\twomen|dobj\tor|cc\ttreat us as if they were victims|conj\tus|dobj\tas|mark\tif|mark\tthey|nsubj\tas if they were victims|advcl\tvictims|attr\t,|punct\tthere|expl\ta|det\tthat|nsubj\tto|aux\tbe|auxpass"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many maxims have there been in the past?",
                    "score": 0.5531,
                    "answers": "of maxims that continue to be repeated today|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the maxims that continue to be repeated today?",
                    "score": 0.5378,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 11/01/2021 that Evidently there are reluctances , the disqualification of feminism has always been a classic , when they associate it with hatred of men , that what you really want is to de - protect women or treat us as if they were victims , there are a series of maxims that continue to be repeated today|ROOT\ta series of maxims that continue to be repeated today|attr\tmaxims that continue to be repeated today|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "What role do men play in feminist discourse?Men play a very important role, we need them to open their own gap with regard to masculinities, with regard to how they are going to stand before this revolution that directly challenges them.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "What website reported on what role do men play in feminist discourse?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What role do men play in feminist discourse?",
                    "score": 0.8271,
                    "answers": "on 11/01/2021|prep\tthat What role do men play in feminist discourse?Men|ccomp\tin feminist discourse?Men|prep\tfeminist discourse?Men|pobj\tplay a very important role|punct\ta very important role|dobj\ttheir|poss\ttheir own gap with regard to masculinities , with regard to they are going how to stand before this revolution that directly challenges them|dobj\twith regard to masculinities , with regard to they are going how to stand before this revolution that directly challenges them|prep\tregard to masculinities|pobj\tto masculinities|prep\tmasculinities|pobj\twith regard to they are going how to stand before this revolution that directly challenges them|prep\tregard to they are going how to stand before this revolution that directly challenges them|pobj\tto they are going how to stand before this revolution that directly challenges them|prep\thow to stand before this revolution that directly challenges them|xcomp\tbefore this revolution that directly challenges them|prep\tthis revolution that directly challenges them|pobj\tthat directly challenges them|relcl"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "They have their own work to do as individuals and collectively to think about what they are going to do to accelerate the change of men, because the change of women has accelerated greatly and the ones left behind are them.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on 11/01/2021 that they have their own work to do as individuals and collectively to think about what they are going to do to accelerate the change of men?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the change of gender in the world?",
                    "score": 0.5298,
                    "answers": "because the change of women has accelerated greatly and the ones left behind are them|advcl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the trend of women leaving behind men?",
                    "score": 0.5259,
                    "answers": "the ones left behind are them|conj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "How many women were left behind in the change of men?",
                    "score": 0.5207,
                    "answers": "left behind|acl"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What are the statistics on the change of men and women?",
                    "score": 0.5207,
                    "answers": "own|amod\tindividuals|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the current gender gap between men and women?",
                    "score": 0.4967,
                    "answers": "of men|prep\tmen|pobj\tof women|prep\twomen|pobj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Do different ideologies exist in feminism?It cannot be denied that the history of feminism is diverse and plural.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported on feminism on 11/01/2021?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the history of feminism?",
                    "score": 0.8041,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 11/01/2021 that Do different ideologies exist in feminism?It|ROOT\ton 11/01/2021|prep\tthat|mark\tDo|aux\tdifferent|amod\tdifferent ideologies|nsubj\tthat Do different ideologies exist in|ccomp\tin|prep\tfeminism?It|punct\tcan|aux\tnot|neg\tbe|auxpass\tcan not be denied that the history of feminism is diverse and plural|ROOT\tthat|mark\tthe|det\tthe history of feminism|nsubj\tof feminism|prep\tfeminism|pobj\tthat the history of feminism is diverse and plural|ccomp\tdiverse and plural|acomp\tand|cc\tplural|conj"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "claim": "Liberal feminism has already existed in other times, another thing is that we do not lose sight of the fact that the feminist spirit is transformative and necessarily opposed to the conservative.",
            "question_answers": [
                {
                    "question": "Who reported that liberal feminism has already existed in other times?",
                    "answer": "elpais.com"
                }
            ],
            "focal_questions": [
                {
                    "question": "How many times has Liberal feminism existed?",
                    "score": 0.8564,
                    "answers": "other times|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What does elpais.com say about liberal feminism?",
                    "score": 0.8021,
                    "answers": "elpais.com reported on 11/01/2021 that Liberal feminism has already existed in other times , another thing is that we do not lose sight of the fact that the feminist spirit is transformative and necessarily opposed to the conservative|ROOT"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is Liberal feminism?",
                    "score": 0.7924,
                    "answers": "that|mark\tLiberal feminism|nsubj\thas|aux\talready|advmod\tthat Liberal feminism has already existed in other times|ccomp\tin other times|prep\tother|amod\t,|punct\tanother|det\tanother thing|nsubj\tthat|mark\twe|nsubj\tdo|aux\tnot|neg\tthat we do not lose sight of the fact that the feminist spirit is transformative and necessarily opposed to the conservative|ccomp\tof the fact that the feminist spirit is transformative and necessarily opposed to the conservative|prep\tthe|det\tthe fact that the feminist spirit is transformative and necessarily opposed to the conservative|pobj\tthat|mark\tthe|det\tfeminist|amod\tthat the feminist spirit is transformative and necessarily opposed to the conservative|acl\ttransformative and necessarily opposed to the conservative|acomp\tand|cc\tnecessarily|advmod\tto the conservative|prep\tthe|det\tthe conservative|pobj"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the source of evidence of Liberal feminism?",
                    "score": 0.7594,
                    "answers": "on 11/01/2021|prep"
                },
                {
                    "question": "What is the history of liberal feminism?",
                    "score": 0.7481,
                    "answers": "sight of the fact that the feminist spirit is transformative and necessarily opposed to the conservative|dobj"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}